Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey! Don't move!
- He got shot. He needs a hospital.
-  Where's Alice?
- There's been a change of plans.
- Meaning?
Guys... I'm dying here.
- You left the Maserati for me?
- Don't remind me. It wasn't easy.
Genny. I need you to pay all my debts.
It's quite a lot.
You're not dying. Tancredi.
Who gets the convertible?
Daniel does.
Mm. Kissing ass to the bitter end.
You're gonna be fine.
Don't lie to me. man!
Give it to me straight!
It's a scratch.
The bullet barely even touched you.
What?
But I saw my entire life flash
before my eyes.
- Was it disappointing?
- It was pretty disappointing actually.
I need more gunfights.
Can we get back to Alice. please?
What happened in there?
They threatened Adele.
she flinched. they got her.
- What does Laurent want with her?
- Not her. me.
He wants me to rob the necklace for him.
So are we not going to the hospital now?
No.
Oh.
My father was wrong to trust you.
And so was I.
You're just like my sister.
We can get her back.
You gotta help me.
Walk me through the security plan
for the auction.
I'm calling the police.
Come on. Adele.
You know what? Here. Go ahead.
I spent hours looking for this.
Alice was protecting you.
Me?
They said they would hurt you if she left.
so she stayed. for you.
It was you they were after all along
to help with this robbery. not her.
Bruno fucked up and got the wrong sister.
I can get her back.
Trust me.
Once the auction is underway.
all access to the hotel will be sealed.
There will be a perimeter.
The guests will be all around here.
The remote bidders over here
and the Callas necklace will be there.
In bulletproof crystal.
There will be armed guards
on the road. the pier.
the beach
and all around the grounds.
Some you will see.
Some you will not.
They keep things friendly.
but make no mistake.
These guys are serious.
Yeah. I don't think I'm a heist guy.
There's way too many variables here.
We're not prepped for this.
- Bystanders. friendlies. guns...
- You've got homecourt advantage.
You can figure it out.
Yeah. what if I don't?
You can do this.
Do what?
For the record. Mr. Caetani. I was never
fully on board with the whole heist idea.
Rabble-talk.
All of you...
Out!
Where is my daughter?
Dad?
We have to leave.
the police will be here anytime now.
They won't.
The police won't come.
Isn't it true. my dear?
Go fuck yourself.
You are not the wrong sister.
You and Daniel were sent to me.
Maria Callas wants me
to have that necklace.
Dad. please.
Dad?
You have no poetry.
Go away.
Get my things.
Get in!
Come on!
I see everything so clearly now.
After my N.D.E.
Who's Andy?
N.D.E.
Near Death Experience.
I'll give you a near death experience.
Your threats mean nothing to me now.
I am a new man.
I think you have
the same fuckface as yesterday.
- Oh. no. That is...
- Shh. Guys... Guys. kinda...
Steal it?
Absolutely not.
Laurent is obsessed.
We gotta take him seriously.
Well. why didn't you shoot him then?
Isn't that what soldiers do?
We have to trust Daniel. It's his job.
Daniel. can you do it?
Can you steal it?
Not safely. no.
- I can't.
- I believe you.
It's too dangerous for my guests.
for my hotel and my daughter.
- If something goes wrong...
- I won't let that happen. sir.
There has to be another way.
Well. if we can't steal it...
We win it.
We win a 15-million-dollar necklace?
At auction?
Against my richest guests?
With what?
All of it?
Yes.
Against the hotel.
the other house.
the little boat and the stocks?
I can raise the line of credit
to maybe 14.
-  Make it 15 million.
- Augusto...
Villa Costiera
is worth a hundred. Get it done.
Go get the clowns.
You mean my team?
I need to teach you all
a couple of things about money.
This is not the first time
we hold an auction here.
People think they're about buying things.
They're not.
- They're not?
- No. Count Rochester.
They're about ego.
Auctions are competitions.
You play the players.
not the money.
In the heat of it. things change quickly.
Madmen back out.
Casuals go rabid.
Trolls hike the price.
Few people go in
knowing where they will stop.
and almost no one comes out happy.
These are the bidders
who registered for tonight.
I suggest you study.
See who you are up against
and what they want.
Learn when to go high
and when to stay put.
Adele and I cannot bid at our own party.
So we'll use our coolest player.
I accept the challenge.
I mean Daniel.
Oh. of course.
The Frenchman has my daughter.
The expected sale price
is 12.5 million euros.
You have 15.
Your opponents have unlimited cash.
Do the math.
You do this my way. by the book.
No tricks.
nothing that puts Alice at risk.
You have to promise me.
I promise.
My wife used to paint in here.
The spaghetti at the table...
Sorry.
Alright. Let's get to work.
Excuse me a second.
Hey!
Uhm... Hi.
How are you?
It's good to hear.
Alright. well. look. I was wondering...
How would you like
to come to a fancy gala in Villa Costiera?
Do you know she stayed
with the French to keep me safe? Me.
She must be driving them crazy.
can you imagine?
Good morning. little one!
Show her.
Welcome to your new home.
Or maybe the last one.
Who knows?
Oh. Sabine...
Oh!
French craftsmanship.
Dreadful.
Like English food.
Tread lightly. heathen.
Only about half a dozen of these guys are
real players willing to go the distance.
The rest is just here for show.
There's lobster tonight.
I don't want to spoil my appetite.
- Shut up and eat.
-  Shall we get started?
Ramon Maria Hernandez. football superstar.
worth about 20 of these necklaces.
But it is his Latvian model
mistress who wears the cleats.
She's a failed opera singer.
Next up we have Henrik Van Heerden.
"Van Heerden Diamonds".
South Africa.
He wants to pry those jewels off
and double his money.
Iason Athanasiou.
Son of the Greek shipping magnate.
Wants to gift the necklace
to the Athens Museum.
- Just to piss daddy off.
-  Mm.
Lord Fabian Selby-Wicker.
British collector. Peer of the Realm.
Almost as crazy about
the necklace as Laurent. apparently.
My mother hates the man.
Positively froths at him.
And finally we have...
Mangia... Man... Mangia...
Mahendra Chandrasekar.
Telecoms India.
About half the market.
Half the fucking market.
Alright. let us not forget this back row.
our remote bidders.
This back wall is lined with folks
who are calling in from hedge funds.
We got tech bros. pop stars
and several banks.
Thank you for flying me in.
Keys to the power shed.
From there. in a pinch you can kill
the lights and landlines.
As well as the hotel
and my career and my life.
Not a problem.
Call it "Plan B".
Smash and grab.
Wow. look at you.
Settle down. Genny.
I don't wanna go to jail.
Hopefully we don't have to use them.
We get sketchy.
those guards will get jumpy.
I'd say we're pretty sketchy now.
I used to steal necklaces all the time.
My daddy was a bank robber.
- Oh. great song.
- I know.
Let's suit up. huh?
Go win this thing. Great work.
Why the fuck
do I keep cooking if nobody eats?
- Right...
- No.
Wow...
What?
I'm starting to look like my old man.
Your dad?
Natty dresser. was he?
Yeah.
What?
You look great.
Don't you have an auction to rig?
Excuse me. "rig"?
I mean to win that thing fair and square.
Sure you do.
You... have some outlaw in you.
Daniel De Luca.
'Round here we call it "scugnizzo".
"Scugnizzo".
Close enough.
Hi.
People always say
you feel nothing when you get shot.
But you do feel things.
Mainly pain.
Then... then it all goes black.
And you know what?
There is a light at the end of the tunnel.
What kind of light?
I mean. technically I was dead.
You were dead?
Yes.
I was dead.
You doing okay?
You think we can win it?
It'll be tight. but yeah.
Yeah. I do.
And will this asshole
keep his end of the deal?
Of course!
I always do.
I fucking knew it.
Touché.
Ah. the serious sister.
Finally. Enchanté.
Such a beautiful hotel.
You and your father kicked me out of here
when I was a child.
- How's the shoulder doing. Ratatouille?
-  Oh. fine.
You're a terrible shot.
I think you mean generous.
If you harm my daughter...
Deliver the necklace and she will be fine.
- When are you doing the switch?
- That's none of your business.
It should be easy.
I gave you everything you need.
Your fake necklace is a piece of shit
that keeps falling apart.
Wait...
You're not switching it?
You're buying it for me?
No... It's too good.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to the auction
for the Maria Callas necklace.
Now. without further ado.
please welcome the star of tonight's show.
Isn't she exquisite?
She certainly is.
I'm looking for 2.6.
ladies and gentlemen. 2.6.
Hernandez? Thank you. sir. 2.6.
I'm looking for 2.8.
2.8. ladies and gentlemen.
2.7?
2.7. Cagliostro.
Thank you. madam. 2.7.
2.75. 3 million...
Daniel?
- Yeah?
- You okay?
Do you not want to bid?
Uh. not yet.
Telecom guy's itching
for a fight over there.
Guess this might take a while.
Slow is good. Genny.
Slow... is good.
It's slow alright.
Rich people are stingy.
3.25?
There it is. I've got you.
3.3 if we can. 3.3?
I'm going 3.35. Can you give me 3.4?
Good evening. madam.
Tancredi Villanova-Rochester.
Thank you there. 3.8.
3.8 down here.
Thank you very much indeed.
3.85 if we can.
3.85. in the middle. 3.85.
9 million 150 for De Luca!
Do I have 9.2?
9.2. 9.2. please.
In the room if we can.
9.2 on the remote. Thank you.
- Fuck!
- Do I have 9.25?
I'm looking for 9.25. De Luca?
De Luca. I'm gonna have to push you
on 9.25. Can I get that from you. sir?
-  Why not?
- The remote guys are bored.
No need to wake them up.
I don't want to turn this
into a pissing contest.
This whole thing
is one giant pissing contest.
9.35?
Chandrasekhar. 9.35.
- 9.4? Back to Van Heerden. For 9.4.
- Where the hell is she?
Where's who?
Right at the back. 9.45.
Thank you. 9.45.
Alright. well. glass half full.
It's not every day I get to go
on a 9 million quid date.
I mean. technically I was dead...
What are you doing here?
They're playing bazaar.
With my daughter's life. in my house.
I know. Come on. let's go back inside.
You didn't want this life. I know.
No. that's not true.
I decided everything for you.
For everyone. And look at us now.
At least now you can leave this place
behind and travel. see the world.
But I don't want
to leave this place behind.
This is my home. dad.
It's in my blood.
Yes. it's in your blood.
13 million 154. Van Heerden.
Do I have 13.2?
13.2 remote. Thank you.
Do I have 13.3?
Ladies and gentlemen. 13.3?
13.3. Chandrasekar.
13.4. Athanasiou. Thank you. sir.
- 13.5?
- Yeah.
Thank you very much. De Luca.
Right in the middle. 13.5.
13.6. 13.6 is on the remote.
Thank you very much. 13.7?
This is going too fast.
- 13.7 in the room.
- Yeah.
13.7. De Luca. Thank you. sir.
13.8 if we can.
Thank you very much.
Chandrasekar. 13.8.
I'm looking for 13.9.
Looking for 13.9 in the room.
Sorry.
This is from Mr. De Luca.
If we can. 13.9?
13... 13.9.
I beg your pardon.
ladies and gentlemen. 13.9.
Looking for 13.9. 13.9...
Thank you very much indeed. sir.
13.9.
14 million if we can. 14 million.
14 and a half million!
14.5. Lord Selby Wicker.
thank you very much indeed. sir.
Welcome to the auction. 14.5.
Can I get any advance on 14.5
from Lord Selby-Wicker?
14.6 on the remote.
Thank you very much indeed. madam. 14.6.
I'm looking for 14.7.
Lord Fabian?
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Tancredi Villanova-Rochester.
I believe you have met my mother.
the Countess.
At Bellagio. or maybe Gstaad.
Bugger off!
14.8. Thank you very much. 14.9.
'08 or maybe '06.
I was very little at the time.
I said. "bugger off"!
15 million!
15 million. Lord Selby-Wicker!
Any advance. ladies and gentlemen.
on 15 million?
Down here. to my right.
- What's going on?
- Do you have any extra money?
Anywhere?
- Do you?
- I don't even have 15.
Right. okay.
Okay.
Daniel. do whatever you need to do.
Yes. sir.
- Hey!
- Sweetheart! I'm sorry I'm late.
The jet wouldn't start and then I realized
I forgot my passport at home!
- I had to go all the way back!
- We've all been there.
You're right on time. it's no problem.
I have a little favour to ask of you.
Mm... You look yummy.
So do you. Thank you.
You look great.
So. I just have this favour
and it is a big one. honestly.
So. are you ready?
I suppose I do owe you. don't I?
You do. technically. actually.
So. I need you to go into this auction
and win with your ex-husband's money.
I'm sorry. what?
I've already got 15 million.
so really. technically.
you're probably not gonna spend that much.
I just need you
to finish the bidding with me.
It's very important.
Are you not going
to wine and dine me first?
I was gonna wine and dine you.
That's what we would have been doing
if you weren't five hours late. okay?
Four.
My apologies.
How much money do you need?
You know what?
Let's go find out. okay?
It's a live auction. so it's...
I don't even like that necklace.
It's so old!
I wouldn't choose it. okay?
But listen. do you remember Alice.
the missing girl?
- The daughter?
- Yes.
- Did you find her?
- I did. And then I didn't. I did...
I need to get this necklace.
so they don't kill her.
- What?
- I know.
They have her.
I didn't wanna scare you.
- Oh. my God!
- I know. I know. It's okay. It's crazy.
But all you need to do to fix that
is buy the necklace.
You lend it to me. I get it back to you
no later than tomorrow morning.
and you've saved her life. okay?
Believe in me again.
I believe you.
Great. Okay.
On my signal. yeah?
But no.
I'm not going to buy it.
-  What's that?
- I thought this was a date.
This is an auction for somebody's life.
That's weird.
Hey. are you still hanging around
with Genny?
Can we talk about that another time. please?
No. no. no...
- Sorry. honey.
- Oh...
There is an island I want to buy.
I want to repopulate the turtles.
It's for the planet.
Climate change?
I don't think that means
what you think it means.
- Okay...
- Mmm...
You look so sad.
But still yummy. though.
17.7. ladies and gentlemen.
17.7. I'm looking for 17.7.
17.7. Athanasiou.
Thank you very much indeed. 17.7.
I'm looking for 17.8.
17.8 on the remote.
17.9 if we can.
17.9? 17.9. Van Heerden.
Thank you. sir. again.
17.9. 18.
Looking for 18.
Looking for 18 million.
18 million right in the middle there.
Thank you. sir.
Plan B?
Plan B.
Genny?
The lights.
How long do you think it'll take
to shut the power down?
30 seconds. give or take.
20 million for Mr. Van Heerden!
Is there any advance on 20 million
for Mr. Van Heerden?
In that case. 20 million is going once.
ladies and gentlemen.
20 million going twice.
20 million going three times!
And...
25 million!
Is it dollars or pounds?
Is that Sheryl fucking Tarsky?
- The auction is in euros. Miss...
- Sheryl!
It is.
Except for the "fucking Tarsky" part.
Okay. 25 million euros then.
Who invited her?
I'm thinking Daniel.
Genny.
Bignè?
Are you registered to bid here
this evening?
Yes.
She is.
In case anyone's thinking
of getting pushy.
there is plenty more money
where that came from.
Very well.
In that case.
unless there is any advance.
25 million is going once...
25 going twice...
Going three times...
And... sold for 25 million euros!
To Miss Sheryl... Congratulations!
Yes! Yes!
- Ye... Yes!
- Okay.
This way. please.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I thought you were capable.
But you're just a concierge.
- I have the necklace.
- No. you don't!
I'm getting... Laurent!
Deliver it in three hours. if you have it!
Shit!
Sabine...
What do we do now?
If they don't bring us the necklace.
we get rid of the girl and leave.
I'm a thief. not a murderer.
As you wish.
Are you sure you don't want us
to take it back to the vault for you?
No. No. I'm good. Thank you.
Amazing.
You may lift your perimeter off my hotel.
Thank you.
You must be very proud.
I guess.
Hey.
Thank you.
Hey. rascal.
Hey. yourself.
Look at that.
Now I owe you one. Big time.
Yes. you do.
And the necklace. you know...
It's rather growing on me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Maybe I want to keep it.
Maybe you should. Tomorrow.
- I don't even...
- Are we going or what?
Hey...
Hi. Genny. Good to see you.
Careful. Daniel.
Taking one for the team
can turn into a habit.
Genny. that's not what...
Damn it.
Uhm...
Thank you. I gotta go. I gotta go.
Thank you.
Le Bris?
It's time.
Time to go home!
Good morning. princess.
Big day. huh?
Thanks.
I thought I was going back home!
They don't want you back home.
Wait.
-  What?
- I have it.
That is good.
I will send you coordinates
for my yacht.
Drop the necklace!
Bruno...
I got somewhere to be.
Drop it! Drop or I shoot!
- You're not that guy. Bruno.
-  Yes. I am!
You're doing this to me!
You're doing this!
I only wanted...
Ah!
Eight out of ten.
Eight?
Let's see...
You know. Bruno...
I feel like if we met in another life.
we could be friends.
Really?
Gentlemen.
Where is she?
Bring her here!
You okay?
- Slow night... You?
- Hey!
The necklace.
The real thing.
I thought you lost the auction.
I got a good team.
- You should come work with us.
-  I'm good. actually.
Uh-uh.
Alice first.
Necklace first.
You know what? Same time.
Or maybe we shoot you.
It might get a little messy.
You will get the girl
when we are far away from here.
That wasn't the deal.
The deal changed.
Did it?
What are you doing?
- You... you wouldn't!
- No?
Ah!
What did you do?
Go look for it! Go. jump!
Ah!
Yes! There!
Daniel!
Yes! Well done. son!
I'm coming!
Thank you. son.
Give it to me!
Come on! Come on!
Little help?
Ah...
Are you okay?
Oh...
Looks like your fake one.
You son...
of a bitch...
Shit!
What are we doing?
Waiting.
I didn't kiss Sheryl. you know.
You didn't kiss me either.
Guys... is this what I think it is?
Dad. we have to go.
Dad?
Dad. the police are coming.
Hey!
Daniel...
Let's go. Come.
-  As promised...
- Mmm...
You are a life saver. Thank you. really.
I'm gonna be able
to sell this thing off. right?
Not here. you won't. No more auctions.
- Hey. no. Seriously.
- No. no. no.
He'll find you a buyer. I promise. Really.
-  A toast.
- Oh. God.
Isn't it a little early. guys?
Oh. shut up and drink.
I'd like to speak to you about your son.
My son?
Yes. your son...
Daniel De Luca.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm